const store = [
  {
    question:'Besides being an actor what other proffesions has Donald done in his career?',
    answers: [
      'Writer',
      'Basketball player',
      'Programmer',
      'Ac repair'
      ],
    correctAnswer:'Writer',
  },
  {
    question:'Donald glover had a net Worth of how many million?',
    answers:[
      '1 Million',
      '7 Million',
      '12 Million',
      '22 Million'
      ],
    correctAnswer:'12 Million',
  },
  {
    question:'Before acting in the show Community what tv show did Donald write for?',
    answers:[
      'The Voice',
      '30 Rock',
      'The Blacklist',
      'This Is Us'
      ],
    correctAnswer:'30 Rock',
  },
  {
    question:'Where is Donald Glover from?',
    answers:[
      'Atlanta,GA',
      'Stone Mountain,GA',
      'Nashville,TN',
      'New York,NY'
      ],
    correctAnswer:'Stone Moutaine,GA',
  },
  {
    question:'Where does the rap name "Childish Gambino" come from?', 
    answers:[
      'Childhood nickname',
      'Donalds stand up comedy career',
      'Wu-tang name generator ',
      'Family name'
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Wu-tang name generator '
  },
  {
    question:'What role did Glover play in the 2017 film Solo: AStar Wars movie?', 
    answers:[
      'Hans Solo',
      'Lando Calrissian',
      'Beckett',
      'Chewbacca'
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Lando Calrissian'
  },
  {
    question:'Which of these albums was the most recent for Donald Glover?',
    answers:[
      'Camp',
      'Because of the Internet',
      'Awaken My Love!',
      'Royalty'
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Awaken My Love!'
  },
  {
    question:'In high school he was voted most likely to write for what show?',
    answers:[
      'The Simpsons',
      'Family Guy',
      'South Park',
      'Futurama'
    ],
    correctAnswer:'The Simpsons'
  },
  {
    question:' How many  youtube views did the song "This is America" recieve in its first week',
    answers:[
      '200 Million',
      '150 Million',
      '1 Million',
      '800 thousand'
    ],
    correctAnswer:'150 Million'
  }, 
  {
    question:'What does the Gambino music video "This Is America" Depict',
    answers:[
      'The american dream',
      'American culture of dance and hip hop',
      'Gun violence and mass killings',
      'Terrorist issues in America'
    ],
    correctAnswer:'Gun violence and mass killings'
  },     

  ];
